<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CareSwift</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="faq_text">FAQs (Frequently Asked Questions):\n\n1. Q: What services does CareSwift offer?\n   A: CareSwift provides a range of health-related services, including appointment scheduling, medication tracking, and health monitoring.\n\n2. Q: How can I schedule a medical appointment through CareSwift?\n   A: Simply log in to your account, navigate to the \"Appointments\" section, and follow the steps to schedule an appointment with your preferred healthcare provider.\n\n3. Q: Is my personal health information secure with CareSwift?\n   A: Yes, we take the security and privacy of your health information seriously. CareSwift employs industry-standard measures to safeguard your data.</string>
    <string name="company_location_text">Company Location:\n\nCareSwift Headquarters:\n123 Health Street,\nWellness City, Medtopia</string>
    <string name="about_us_text">About Us:\n\nWelcome to CareSwift, your comprehensive healthcare companion. At CareSwift, we are committed to revolutionizing the way you manage your health. Our services include:\n\n Appointment Scheduling: Easily book medical appointments with your preferred healthcare providers.\n- Medication Tracking: Stay on top of your medication schedule with timely reminders.\n Health Monitoring: Track and monitor vital health metrics for a proactive approach to well-being.\n Personalized Health Insights: Receive insights and recommendations based on your health data.\n\nAt CareSwift, your health and well-being are our top priorities. We strive to empower you with the tools and information needed for a healthier, happier life.</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions_text">Terms and Conditions:\n\n1. User Responsibility:\n   Users are responsible for the accuracy and completeness of the information provided.\n   Users must adhere to ethical usage and respect the privacy of others on the platform.\n\n2. Data Security:\n   CareSwift employs industry-standard measures to secure user data.\n   Users are advised to keep login credentials confidential to prevent unauthorized access.\n\n3. Service Availability:\n   CareSwift strives to maintain uninterrupted service; however, interruptions may occur for maintenance or unforeseen circumstances.\n\n4. Termination of Account:\n   CareSwift reserves the right to terminate or suspend user accounts for violation of terms or misuse of the platform.</string>
</resources>